

[
   
      {
        "question": "Greek teacher or philosophy, reasoning , and public speaking",
        "choice1": "sophists",
        "choice2": "rhetoric",
        "choice3": "socratic method",
        "choice4": "hippocratic oath",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "The study of the basic ideas about society, education, and right and wrong.  Basic beliefs, concepts, and attitudes",
        "choice1": "philosophy",
        "choice2": "absolute truth",
        "choice3": "Plato",
        "choice4": "Aristotle",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "the art of public speaking and debate",
        "choice1": "sophists",
        "choice2": "rhetoric",
        "choice3": "socratic method",
        "choice4": "hippocratic oath",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "Philosophical method or questioning to gain truth",
        "choice1": "sophists",
        "choice2": "rhetoric",
        "choice3": "socratic method",
        "choice4": "hippocratic oath",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "A set of promises about patient care that new electors make when they start practicing medicine",
        "choice1": "sophists",
        "choice2": "rhetoric",
        "choice3": "socratic method",
        "choice4": "hippocratic oath",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "what means love and wisdom",
        "choice1": "philosophy",
        "choice2": "absolute truth",
        "choice3": "Plato",
        "choice4": "Aristotle",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Socrates believed in ____________ ",
        "choice1": "philosophy",
        "choice2": "absolute truth",
        "choice3": "Plato",
        "choice4": "Aristotle",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was a student of Socrates and wrote in the Republic",
        "choice1": "philosophy",
        "choice2": "absolute truth",
        "choice3": "Plato",
        "choice4": "Aristotle",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "Who wrote the book, politics and was a student of Plato",
         "choice1": "philosophy",
        "choice2": "absolute truth",
        "choice3": "Plato",
        "choice4": "Aristotle",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is considered the fater of history",
        "choice1": "Herodotus",
        "choice2": "Pythagorus",
        "choice3": "Plato",
        "choice4": "Socrates",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Who taught that the universe was governement by the same laws as music and numbers",
        "choice1": "Herodotus",
        "choice2": "Pythagorus",
        "choice3": "Aristotle",
        "choice4": "Sparta",
        "answer": 2
      }
]
